Ishsta Glass

Ishstaglass@yahoo.com | (918) 289-7012 | Yukon, OK 73099

Summary

IT Technician with 4 years of experience and a great work ethic. Knowledge and training of some sort in all aspects of IT as well as being knowledgeable in HTML, CSS, Javascript, and Python.

Skills

- Component repairs
- Computer skills
- Friendly, positive attitude
- HTML
- CSS
- Terminal
- Python

- Microsoft Office
- Application installations
- Troubleshooting and diagnostics
- Javascript
- GIT

Experience

End User Device Analyst- OU Health (Oklahoma City, OK) March 2022 - June 2022 (contract)

- Install, deploy, and test equipment and software per standards and guidelines, including but not limited to terminals, personal computers, printers, cabling, and related software products.
- Performs facility-based moves, adds, and changes (MACs), as needed.
- Effectively works with customers, Service Desk and Technical Services personnel.
- Work within large datasets, taking care to maximize the accuracy and security of endpoint information.

Bench Technician - Dynamic Gaming Solutions (Oklahoma City, OK) March 2021 - March 2022

- Troubleshot malfunctions and diagnosed issues to service equipment quickly and fully.
- Installed new components or replaced defective parts to restore functionality.
- Repaired components such as circuit boards, monitors, printers, and bill acceptors.

IT Technician II - CT Technologies (Ponca City, OK) September 2017 - March 2021

- Maintained hardware performance, network connectivity, and software updates in a casino environment with 100+ employees.
- POS troubleshooting and set up
- VoIP phone system
- Responded to or escalated tickets based on severity and internal policies governing responses.
- Coordinated ticket fulfillment among multiple technicians and teams to reduce redundancy and accelerate response times.

• Removed malware and viruses from laptops and desktop systems using specialized software.

Guest Service Representative - Kaw Southwind Casino (Newkirk, OK) March 2017 - September 2017

- Addressed and welcomed large volume of guests to business per day, improving overall customer service and engagement.
- Managed customer complaints and rectified issues to complete satisfaction.
- Help to resolve customer disputes in ways the customer themselves understood.
- Handled large amounts of money accurately.

Field Technician/Slot Technician - Integrity Gaming (Tonkawa, OK) June 2016 - August 2016

- Performed annual and preventive system service maintenance.
- Completed repairs, performed preventive maintenance and kept records in quality system.
- Performed mechanical and electrical work on slot machines.

Education and Training

High School Diploma

May 2016

Big Pasture High School, Randlett, OK